devskiller.com 2019-06-03

# Privacy policy - Devskiller - Powerful tool to test developers skills

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Devskiller.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the [https://devskiller.com](https://devskiller.com/) site (“Site”). This Privacy Policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Devskiller.com.

  1. PERSONAL DATA 

1.1. Personal data provided by Users within the frames of the Site are processed by Devskiller.com, the Personal Data Controller, in accordance with the terms prescribed by Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 (hereinafter referred to as “GDPR”). You may contact the Data Controller via e-mail at legal@devskiller.com

1.2. The scope of processed data is determined by the contact form completed by the User, which is sent to Devskiller.com and includes the e-mail address, name of the User and additionally, the computer IP address. Personal data of Users, upon prior consent of the User, may be used for contact with Users and may be shared with third-party entities for the purpose of sending newsletter and displaying advertisements.

1.3. Your personal data will be processed for the following purposes: (a) provision of services by electronic means, (b) promotional or marketing actions of Devskiller.com. 

1.4. Your personal data will be processed for the period of 5 years and will be deleted upon the lapse of the said period, unless their processing results from another legal basis. 

1.5. The legal basis of processing within the site is consent of the data subject.

1.6. Your personal data may be transferred for processing to (recipients of personal data): Devskiller.com’s accounting firm, the provider of hosting for the Site, the company providing technical support for the Site, the payment provider, the company providing the CRM system. The personal data collected by Devskiller.com may also be disclosed to: competent state authorities upon their request on the basis of relevant provisions of law or other persons and entities—in the cases prescribed in the provisions of law. The entity processing Users’ personal data on the basis of the Transfer Agreement will process Users’ personal data from the effective date of GDPR through another entity only upon prior consent of Devskiller.com

1.7. Personal data of the Site Users will be processed in the form of profiling on the basis of the number of sessions on Users’ pages. The User may file an objection to profiling via e-mail at legal@devskiller.com.

1.8. Devskiller.com may disclose User’s personal data to other entities only upon User’s prior consent. 

1.9. You have right to: remove the collected personal data referring to you both from the Devskiller.com system and from bases of entities which have co-operated with Devskiller.com, to restrict the processing of data and the right to portability of the personal data collected by Devskiller.com and referring to the User and to receive them in a structured form, to file a complaint to the supervisory authority if the User finds that his/her data are processed in violation of the law, and to seek legal remedies before a court against the supervisory authority as the entity committing the violation.

1.10. Transfer of personal data to third countries will proceed in accordance with GDPR.

1.11. We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, e-mail address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users may always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site-related activities.

  2. NON-PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION 

2.1. We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the utilized Internet service providers and other similar information.

  3. INFORMATION SECURITY

3.1. Devskiller.com additionally applies within the Site all necessary technical measures as specified in Articles 25, 30, 32–34, 35–39 of GDPR, providing for enhanced protection and security of the processing of your personal data. 

3.2. The use of the Site proceeds in secure https connection. The communication between a User’s device and the servers is encoded by means of the SSL protocol. In the case of logging through external platforms facebook.com, twitter.com, Instagram, and   the level of security is prescribed by [https://pl-pl.facebook.com/privacy/explanation](https://pl-pl.facebook.com/privacy/explanation) and    [https://twitter.com/en/privacy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy) and https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy

  4. WEB BROWSER COOKIES 

4.1. Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. Users web browser places cookies on his/her hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set his/her web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert him/her when cookies are being sent. If the User does so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

  5. HOW DO WE USE COLLECTED INFORMATION 

5.1. Devskiller.com may collect and use Users’ personal information for the following purposes:

– to improve customer service. Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

– to improve our Site.

5.2. We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services, to run promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature, to send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them, to send periodic e-mails, after their prior consent.

5.3. We may use the e-mail address to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.

5.4. Cookie files are used for the following purposes: 

  1. a) adjustment of the content of the Site pages to User’s preferences and optimisation of the use of pages; in particular such files enable recognising Site User’s device and correctly displaying the site adjusted to his/her individual needs; 
  2. b) preparation of statistics which help to understand how the Site Users use sites, which enable improving their structure and content; 
  3. c) preparation of recipients list and displaying advertisements adjusted to their needs and interests.

5.5. Within the Site two basic types of cookies are used: session and persistent cookies. Session cookies are temporary files stored on the User’s device until logging out, leaving a site or shutting down the software (the browser). Persistent cookies are stored on the User’s device for a time prescribed in the parameters of the cookie files or until they are removed by the User upon User’s consent. 

5.6. Within the Site the following types of cookies are used:

  1. a) essential cookies enabling the use of services available within the Site, e.g. authenticating cookies used for services requiring authentication within the Site;
  2. b) cookies designed to provide for security, e.g. used to detect abuses in the scope of authentication within the Site;
  3. c) performance cookies enabling the collection of information on the manner in which the Site pages are used;
  4. d) functional cookies enabling to remember User’s settings and to personalise User’s interface, e.g. in terms of a selected language or region where the User is located, the font size, page layout etc.;
  5. e) advertising cookies, which are created by third-party companies (such as AdRoll). They enable provision of advertising content to Users while they visit other websites which fits their interests more, insofar as the User consents to this through settings of his/her browser.

  6. HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION 

6.1. We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

  7. SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

7.1. We do not sell, trade, or rent Users’ personal identification information to others. We may share generic, aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and Users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

7.2. In many cases software designed to browse sites (a browser) allows for storing cookies on the User’s device, insofar as the User selects such option in the browser settings. The Site Users may at any time change the settings related to cookies. Such settings may be changed in particular so as to block the automatic cookie support in the browser settings or to notify on each case of placing them on the Site User’s device. Detailed information on possibilities and methods of cookie support is available in the software (browser) settings.

7.3. Cookies placed on the Site User’s device may also be used by advertisers and partners co-operating with the Site operator upon prior User’s consent given in the browser settings. In accordance with the e-Privacy Regulation, the User may disable the storing of third-party cookies on his/her device in line with the instructions of the browser producer. 

7.4. Failure to enable third-party cookies and cookies other than session cookies may not cause lack of availability of the Site, in part or in its entirety, for the User.

  8. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY 

8.1. Devskiller.com may at its discretion update this Privacy Policy at any time. In such case, we will revise the date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we help to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

  9. YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS

9.1. By using this Site, you declare your acceptance of this Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

  10. CONTACTING US

10.1. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
[Devskiller.com](https://devskiller.com/), [https://devskiller.com](https://devskiller.com/) Lindleya 16, Warsaw, Poland  
+44 20 3876 6444, hello@devskiller.com

This document was last updated on May 24, 2018
